The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Master, oh Master...
Normally, I can only appear when summoned.
But now that you're unconscious,
it seems my chance for freedom has finally come !
Should I attack him ?
He probably isn't faking it, right ?
I won't fall for it.
You can keep pretending.
3 days later
Ah, I can't take it anymore !
I won't ever get a better chance than this !
Fuck it, I'll try !
When did this guy plant his Divine Sense in me ?
Could it be...
Damn it !
Is this how I am supposed to live from now on !?
I really underestimated the difficulty of merging the 3 Cold Cores.
This body simply can't withstand the cold energy released when I try...
I wonder how other cultivators that practiced this method did it.
I've been guarding you the entire time,
I swear !
Go inside.
He's been in closed-door cultivation every day lately.
But forming a Golden Core isn't easy...
The fastest Core Formation in the Burning Fire Country
still took 30 years.
You...
Have you reached a bottleneck ?
Death Spell cultivators need women's Primordial Yin to cultivate...
If he...
You...
I only agreed to make pills for you !
If...
I would rather die than do it !
Why is the Flood Dragon's skull this color ?
The Flood Dragon is poisonous,
it's not strange for its bones to turn purple.
If a Flood Dragon's body contains poison
then how does it avoid being poisoned ?
When the Flood Dragon was alive,
its flesh, blood, bones, and internal organs
and even its saliva contains poison.
So of course it's immune to it.
A body filled with poison...
Since my body cannot withstand the cold energy
that means I need to fill my body with cold energy.
That's how
I will be able to withstand it.
When I reach Core Formation,
I will send you back to the Luo River Sect.
Most of the Corpse Valley is filled with bones
except for this place.
All is this bone-chilling cold that could freeze my soul.
I can only descend this far for now.
If I go any further,
my body,
along with my soul and Divine Sense,
will freeze instantly.
I won't leave this valley
until my Cold Cores are merged !
After some time passed,
the incident of the Fire Spirit Beasts
was solved by a rank 4 country.
But the war between the Burning Fire Alliance and Xuanwu
continued.
The Burning Fire Alliance was able to hold its ground.
Country of Chu
Cloud Sky Sect
Country of Xuanwu
Burning Fire country
War God Shrine
Evil Devil Sect
Corpse Sect
Luo River Sect
After some negotiations,
the situation finally stabilized.
As for Wang Lin, he was focused on cultivating.
The Underworld Ascension Method he cultivates
shouldn't be this difficult.
Note: 1 zhang = 3 meters
This unprecedented difficulty is due to
After 6 months
at a depth of 180 zhang
his heart has beaten
9 837 543 times
the Ji Realm and the Heaven Defying Bead.
After 1 year
at a depth of 730 zhang
his heart has beaten
437 659 times
After 2 years
at a depth of 3627 zhang
his heart has beaten
0 times...
After 3 years
at a depth of
7979 zhang
The Core embryo is formed.
To reach Core Formation
I just need some spiritual energy.
But I'm not confident
in this final push.
If I fail,
the Core embryo will shatter
and I'll have to start over.
Cold energy !
Could this blue flame be the true expression of the Underworld Ascension Method ?
The Underworld Ice Flame !
I never thought I would find more beast bones
this deep underground.
There are so many Spirit Beast bones
that I could try making a reaction furnace
to upgrade my flying sword with.
Crafting a reaction furnace is harder than I expected...
I refuse to believe
that I can't make one furnace
out of this many bones !
Still not enough !
9 colors !
Unfortunately, it's only grade 9.
After all my efforts,
I couldn't make a grade 10 reaction furnace.
Forget it, this will have to do.
Wang Lin didn't know that
even the Sect Leader of the War God Shrine
only possessed a grade 6 reaction furnace.
Using a grade 9 reaction furnace to refine his artifact
is extremely efficient.
Go !
Congratulations on your new life.
Since you swallowed the sword,
where will I live now ?
Note: This is a Flood Dragon's tendon.
Go in.
Now I just need
the Heaven Separating Pill.
South Dipper City is one of the 998 cities in the Sea of Devils.
South Dipper City
Sea of Devils
The city is managed by the Punishing Heaven Sect, Soul Extinguishing Sect,
and the One Heaven Path Sect.
Fellow cultivator, what are you looking for ?
Our Treasure Pavilion has everything.
What's this artifact ?
This is a defensive bracelet
called the Mist-Born Flower.
It has an illusion spell
and women love it.
Why is my cultivation probing failing ?
This person is fluctuating between Core Formation
and Foundation Establishment...
What does Senior need ?
Do you sell pill furnaces ?
Senior, in the entire South Dipper City
our Treasure pavilion
is the only place that sells pill furnaces.
Please follow me to the second floor.
Customer,
please reconsider.
If you buy two, you'll get one for free !
If you're still not satisfied,
take a look at this.
Shopkeeper, the situation is...
The Treasure Pavilion has 3 floors
The attendants on the first floor are at Qi Condensation.
On the second floor, this guy is Foundation Establishment.
Will the third floor
have a Core Formation cultivator ?
Fellow cultivator,
this Mysterious Green Pill Furnace was refined over 49 months
using Greenstar Rock and Mysterious Fog Crystal from the depths of the Sea of Devils.
This is a grade 3 pill furnace.
Li Muwan told me
she needs at least a grade 4 furnace
to guarantee she can refine the Heaven Separating Pill.
I presume fellow cultivator is refining a top quality pill.
This is the Hundred Beasts Pill Furnace, forged from the cores
of 99 low quality beasts
from the Sea of Devils.
If you use it to refine pills,
there will be a chance the pills absorbs the energy of a beast's core.
The furnace's spiritual energy is leaking when it's closed.
When the seal is opened,
this spiritual energy will surge forth !
The Hundred Beasts Spirit Furnace is a grade 5 pill furnace.
The Fighting Evil Sect have been wanting it for a long time
but they lack the funds to buy it
so they never did.
What's the price ?
100 000 high-quality spirit stones !
Or you can offer an artifact of similar value.
This furnace is indeed extremely expensive...
No wonder the Fighting Evil Sect don't have the funds.
Fellow cultivator, would you like another ?
The Mysterious Green Pill Furnace
is only 10 000 high-quality spirit stones.
It can also be used to make many pills.
Flood Dragon hide !
It's real hide from a middle rank Spirit Beast, a Flood Dragon !
How much of this do you have ?
How much for the furnace ?
If the dragon was 1000 zhang long...
the entire hide !
We finally managed to sell that Hundred Beasts Pill Furnace.
The Fighting Evil Sect
lacked the funds to buy it yet acted like it was reserved
and scared everyone from buying it.
Since this person has Flood Dragon hide,
he should be able to protect that pill furnace.
Trading the Flood Dragon hide will attract attention
but it was necessary...
If I were to trade my spirit liquid
it would be even worse.
Someone's been watching me
since I entered the second floor.
Besides the one I marked with my Divine Sense,
there are 3 more Core Formation cultivators.
Elder,
the guy who traded the furnace just left the city.
Kun Sang
Fighting Evil Sect Elder
Early stage Core Formation
Mere tricks !
The hunt begins now !
Pu Lin
Fighting Evil Sect Elder
Early stage Core Formation
Hand over the furnace you bought at the Treasure Pavilion
or die !
Scram !
What kind of flying sword is this !?
If I hadn't slightly dodged it
to avoid a vital spot,
I would've died just now.
Such a flying sword
is extremely rare.
Gu Cheng
Fighting Evil Sect Elder
Early stage Core Formation
This kid must have even more artifacts on him !
If it were just one Core Formation,
I might have a chance.
But facing three at the same time
is troublesome...
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?